#### Contact

03121162343 (Mobile) mzayan97@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ muhammadzayan011 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills
.NET Core
ASP.NET MVC
Augmented Reality (AR)

# Muhammad Zayan

Software Developer | Fintech | Digital Banking Karāchi

### Summary

Experienced Implementation Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in ASP.NET MVC Core Development, C++, English, Augmented Reality (AR) and Adobe Photoshop. Strong information technology professional with a Bachelor of Science - BS focused in Computer Science from NED University of Engineering and Technology.

## Experience

TPS Worldwide Implementation Engineer February 2021 - Present (1 year 1 month) Karāchi, Sindh, Pakistan

Dubai Islamic Bank Senior Dotnet Developer September 2019 - February 2021 (1 year 6 months)

Skill Orbit (Pvt.) Ltd. Employee August 2019 - September 2019 (2 months)

The Nest I/O
Back-end Developer
August 2016 - February 2017 (7 months)
karachi

#### Education

NED University of Engineering and Technology Master of Science - MS, Data Science · (2021 - 2023)

NED University of Engineering and Technology

Bachelor of Science - BS, Computer Science